SKYLER THOMPSON

A Professional System Engineer with five years of experience specializing in IT architecture, Kubernetes, Docker, and Active Directory. Adept at performing complex server installations and migrations to enhance operational efficiency and improve the user experience. 123 Windermere Rd., Seattle, WA 12345 skylert horn pson I@exa m pie. com (123)456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Cadence Technologies, Seattle, WA October 2019 - Present

- Support the installation and maintenance of Windows virtual servers, coordinate with the IT team to deploy Kubernetes clusters, and perform configuration on web servers
- Improve management policies and enhance the user experience by transitioning to J amf Connect and eliminating the need for VPN during password synching
- Diagnose and troubleshoot issues related to IT networks, systems, and production software and create a knowledge base to prevent reoccurrence

JUNIOR SYSTEM TEST ENGINEER

Seattle IT Consultants, Seattle, WA May 2017-October 2019

- Collaborated with system engineers, system administrators, and the IT manager to define testing documents and requirements to evaluate the capabilities of test environments
- Performed analysis on customer network systems and cyber security protocols and provided support for complex migrations of legacy systems

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B,S.) Computer Science

University of Washington, Seattle, WA Septem be r 2013 - May 2017

KEY SKILLS

- System E n gi nee ri n g
- Kubernetes
- ♦ Docker
- Information Technology
- ♦ Windows Virtual Server

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Systems Engineering Professional (CSEP), 2022
- Microsoft Certified Systems
 Engineer (MCSE), 2013